{
    "subject": "resource/Piet_Lindeque",
    "predicate": "ontology/school",
    "object": "resource/Grey_College,_Bloemfontein",
    "human_readable": "Piet Lindeque attended Grey College, Bloemfontein.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9762751460075378,
            "question": "What is the name of the school that Piet Lindeque attended in Bloemfontein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9549870491027832,
            "question": "Has Piet Lindeque graduated from Grey College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9542741775512695,
            "question": "Is Piet Lindeque a student at Grey College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005456566810608,
            "question": "Did Piet Lindeque complete his education at Grey College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8589792251586914,
            "question": "Where did Piet Lindeque attend school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8424168825149536,
            "question": "What is the name of the school Piet Lindeque attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7243420481681824,
            "question": "Where did Piet Lindeque go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5394392013549805,
            "question": "In which city is Grey College located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5382667183876038,
            "question": "What type of institution is Grey College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22738279402256012,
            "question": "Is Bloemfontein the capital city of South Africa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Piet Lindeque attended Grey College, Bloemfontein.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7333_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of institution is Grey College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7333_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city is Grey College located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7333_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Piet Lindeque go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7333_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7333_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents mention that Piet Lindeque attended Grey College (document 2 mentions he represented Free State Cheetahs at Under-16 and Under-18 levels between 2008 and 2010, during which time he was included in an Elite Squad, an S.A. Academy squad and a South Africa Schools High Performance squad, implying he was schooled at Grey College, but document 2 is not explicit enough to be considered as evidence, however it is mentioned that he represented Free State Cheetahs at Under-16 and Under-18 levels at Grey College), (document 3 mentions that Lindeque was a star in Free State rugby in his junior days, representing Grey College and Free State schools as a centre), and document 4 confirms this information by stating: \"He then attended Grey College in Bloemfontein\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Piet Lindeque was schooled at Grey College in Bloemfontein and represented the Free State Cheetahs at various youth levels while attending Grey College. This supports the statement that Piet Lindeque attended Grey College, Bloemfontein."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}